Guide to the Robert Ralph Young Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Audio/Visual Material, Circa 1900s-1950s; Series IV
  - Photographs
    - Business
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 24, Folder 63)
- Oversize, Circa 1900s-1950s
  - Business clippings (Alleghany scrapbook), 1937 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Personal papers
    - Clippings (Young and Moody families), 1909-1985 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Accounts ledgers, 1918-1931 (Box 26, Folder 3-6)
    - Clippings (Robert Young), 1940s-1958 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - "Daring Man of Wall Street" (3 articles on Young by Matthew Josephson), 1945 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Diploma, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Income tax returns (federal), 1918-1925 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Photographs
    - Business
      - General, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - New York Central, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Personal
      - Young, Anita and Eleanor, Circa 1940 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Young, Robert, 1940s-1950s (Box 27, Folder 14-18)